{
  "1": {
    "Question": "What advice does Okoye give to T'Challa before he jumps out of the ship at the start of Black Panther?",
    "Answers": ["Don't freeze","Just don't freeze","When you see her, don't freeze","When you see her don't freeze","dont freeze","just dont freeze","when you see her dont freeze","do not freeze","just do not freeze"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "2": {
    "Question": "Who does Hela say sounds like Odin?",
    "Answers": ["Loki"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "3": {
    "Question": "Aside from Black Panther, in which other MCU film does Ulysses Klaue appear?",
    "Answers": ["Avengers: Age of Ultron"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "4": {
    "Question": "Who is the first Avenger that Tony physically fights? (Hint: they were NOT an Avenger at the time)",
    "Answers": ["James Rhodes"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "5": {
    "Question": "Klaue's vibranium deal sends T'Challa to which nation?",
    "Answers": ["South Korea"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "6": {
    "Question": "Which other hero does Bucky walk out of the portal with onto the battlefield in Avengers: Endgame?",
    "Answers": ["Groot"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "7": {
    "Question": "When Everett Ross wakes up in Shuri's lab and asks if he's in Wakanda, where does Shuri say he is?",
    "Answers": ["Kansas"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "8": {
    "Question": "What name does a frost giant call Thor that causes him to lash out?",
    "Answers": ["Little Princess"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "9": {
    "Question": "Although he goes by Erik Killmonger and has a true Wakandan name, what is Erik's Americanized last name?",
    "Answers": ["Stevens"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "10": {
    "Question": "In order to gain the powers of the Black Panther, one must consume a special herb. What is the shape of that herb?",
    "Answers": ["Heart","Heart-shaped","Heart shaped"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "11": {
    "Question": "What prison are Wanda, Scott, Clint, and Sam being held?",
    "Answers": ["The Raft","Raft","Raft Prison","The Raft Prison"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "12": {
    "Question": "Aside from Bucky, what other Marvel hero appears in the POST-CREDITS scene of Black Panther?",
    "Answers": ["Shuri","Princess Shuri"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "13": {
    "Question": "What phrase is on the receipt for Sam's gear?",
    "Answers": ["Bird costume"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "14": {
    "Question": "How many times does Agent Woo bust into Scott's house unannounced in Ant-Man and the Wasp?",
    "Answers": ["Three","3","three times","3 times","thrice"],
    "DeepCut": []
  },
  "15": {
    "Question": "Who is the only one of the original 6 Avengers to never wield or get hit by Captain America's shield?",
    "Answers": ["Hulk"],
    "DeepCut": []
  }
}
